CURRICULUM VITAE

Personal data

Name: Tomasz Buczek
Date of birth: 05.12.1976

Nationality: Polish

Mobile Number: 733688798 e-mail: tom.buczek@gmail.com

Profile

I am rope access technician with IRATA Level 3.As an IRATA technician I have worked on GSM projects, assembling GSM towers, making swaps and strengthening existing towers and also I took part in the offshore project for "Climb Partner" on Horns Rev 3 in Denmark and Deutsche Bucht. Also I was working for Global Wind Service on Merkur and Deutsche Bucht offshore wind farm as an R A T doing electrician and mechanic scope(service man). Last three years I'm working with Semco Maritime on O&R sector.

Also I am qualified part two scaffolder with 9 years experience. I am trustworthy and hard working person who is ready to undertake new challenges. I am a team player, but I am happy to take initiative if necessary. I have worked on variety projects including industrial scaffolding, railways jobs (PTS qualification), motorways jobs (bridges and viaducts), and domestic work. Lately I'm working offshore, wind farms and oil and rig platforms.

Education

2010	NVQ level 2 in Accessing Operations and Rigging - Scaffolding
2010	Entry level Certificate in Adult Literacy
1995-1998	Technical College in Torun, Poland, profession: laboratory technician
	specialisation: polyester production
1991-1994	Vocational School in Torun, Poland, profession: processing supervisor

Work experience

05.2021 till now

55.1511 tim 1.511	
03.2020-05.2021	"Global Wind Service" Merkur Offshore Wind Farm.
10.2019-12.2020	"RT9-Scandinavian Rope Access" Mersk Interceptor Oilrig Scaffolding Dismantle.
06.2019-07.2019	"Sub C" Rope Access Technician, epoxy job Culzean oil rig North sea.
03.2019-05.2019	"Climb Partner" - Rope Access Technician, mould cleaning Deutsche Bucht wind turbine farm Deutschland.
10.2018 - 02.2019	"Climb Partner" - Rope Access Technician, mould cleaning, Horns Rev 3 wind turbine farm, Denmark
05.2018-10.2018	"Industrial Access Services Ltd, England, glazing and mastic.

"Semco Maritime" RAT electric.mechanic.rigger.scope.

02.2018-05.2018	"RiggTech" – Rope Access Technician, spray painting, Power Station Opole
03.08.2017 till now	"Octopus" Tomasz Buczek, own business
04.2014 - 2017	"Insetox Ltd.", Torun, Poland
12.2010 - 04.2014	"Standard Scaffolding Specialists Ltd.", Bolton, UK
09.20-7 - 12.2010	"Cane Scaffolding Ltd.", Bolton, UK
2006 - 09.2007	"Cape Scaffolding Ltd.", Lynemouth, UK
2005 - 2006	self employed builder,mechanic, UK
2001 - 2005	Rock Climbing Club member (part time scaffolding job), Poland
1998 - 2001	"Insetox Ltd.", Torun, Poland

Training and courses

- 16.11.2023 CompEx
- 19.02.2022 OPITO Rigger, Stage3
- 27.02.2021 IRATA certificate L3.
- 15.01.2020 EE.05-Assembly, start-up and maintenance of installation machines and electric equipment.
- 17.08.2020 BTTW torque and screw connection
- 19.06.2019 MIST
- 17.04.2019 BOSIET whit Ca-ebs
- 17.04.2019 Norwegian Escape Chute
- 15.04.2019 Shoulder Measurement
- 12.04.2019 Confined spaces course
- 22.03.2019 Norsok.M-501
- 22.03.2019 Epoxy
- 09.03.2019 IRATA Certificate of Level 2 Rope Access Technician
- 06.11.2018 OGUK
- 01.10.2018 Asbestos Awareness course
- 20.03.2018 GWO WINDA: TB098273PL
- 25.03.2017 IRATA Certificate of Level 1 Rope Access Technician
- Certificate First Aid in danger to life/in distress/BLS AED Training
- Certificate of qualifying for welder/method TIG
- Erect/Dismantle/and Inspection of Alloy Tower Scaff

Skills

- Ability to work in team, good special skills
- Driving licence cat. B
- PC literate
- English Language fluent in speaking and writing

Interests

Sport, rock climbing, film & music, nature